Guide to the Crawford Theater Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Playbills and Programs, 1663-1989; Series I
  - Subseries C:, 1861-1971; Series I; 6.75 linear feet (27 boxes) Largest dimension: between 13" and 17"
    - United States
      - Ohio
        - Cleveland, 1881-1884, undated (Box 52, Folder 575)
        - Miscellaneous Ohio cities (A-T), 1866-1869, 1882-1886, undated (Box 52, Folder 576)
      - Pennsylvania
        - Philadelphia
          - Alhambra/Alhambra Palace, 1876-1879 (Box 52, Folder 577)
          - Arch Street/Arch Street Opera House, 1886, 1881-1886, undated (Box 52, Folder 578)
          - Chestnut Street/Chestnut Street Opera House, 1871, 1884-1892, 1899, undated (Box 52, Folder 579)
          - Walnut Street, 1871, 1881, 1892 (Box 52, Folder 580)
          - Miscellaneous Philadelphia theaters (A-N), 1871, 1878-1891, 1927 (Box 52, Folder 581)
          - Miscellaneous Philadelphia theaters (P-U); unidentified, 1862, 1879, 1884, 1889, 1938-1939 (Box 52, Folder 582)
        - Miscellaneous Pennsylvania cities (A-P), 1879, 1885-1886, 1890-1891, 1934, undated (Box 52, Folder 583)
      - Rhode Island
        - Providence
          - Opera House, 1872-1873, 1881-1882, undated (Box 52, Folder 584)
          - Miscellaneous Providence theaters (D-W), 1887-1888, undated (Box 52, Folder 585)
      - Tennessee
        - Memphis
          - New Memphis, 1868 (Box 52, Folder 586)
      - Texas, 1888-1890
        - Utah
          - Salt Lake City
            - Salt Lake, 1875 (Box 52, Folder 588)
        - Virginia
          - Richmod, 1890, undated (Box 52, Folder 589)
        - Washington, 1888-1891 (Box 52, Folder 590)
        - Washington, D. C.
          - Albaugh's Grand Opera House, 1888-1893 (Box 52, Folder 591)
          - Belasco, 1905-1906 (Box 52, Folder 592)
          - Columbia, 1905-1906 (Box 52, Folder 593)
          - Ford's/Ford's Athenaeum, 1862-1865 (Box 52, Folder 594)
          - National/New National, 1874, 1881, 1891-1892, 1905-1906 (Box 52, Folder 595)
        - Miscellaneous Washington, D. C. theaters (A-V), 1872, 1892-1893, undated (Box 52, Folder 596)
      - West Virginia
        - Beckley
          - West Virginia Historical Drama Association, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 597)
      - Wisconsin
        - Milwaukee
          - Davidson, 1890, 1900-1901 Sep, 1902-1903 (Box 53, Folder 598-602)
    - Unidentified United States, undated (Box 53, Folder 603)
    - Souvenir programs from U. S. tours of miscellaneous dance companies
      - American Ballet Theatre, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 604)
      - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo, 1938-1940 (Box 53, Folder 604)
      - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo, 1943-1944, 1949-1950 (Box 53, Folder 605)
      - Ballet Theatre, 1943-1945 (Box 53, Folder 605)
      - Black Watch, 1957-1958 (Box 54, Folder 606)
      - Bolshoi Ballet, undated (Box 54, Folder 606)
      - Colonel W. de Basil's Ballets Russes, 1936 (Box 54, Folder 606)
      - Imperial Russian Ballet and Orchestra, 1910 (Box 54, Folder 607)
      - Mia Slavenska, undated (Box 54, Folder 607)
    - Other nations (Box 54, Folder 607)
    - Argentina
      - Buenos Aires
        - Instituto Nacional de Estudios de Teatro, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 608)
    - Australia, 1867, 1885, 1901, undated (Box 54, Folder 609)
    - Austria
      - Vienna, 1887, 1898, 1908, 1925 (Box 54, Folder 610)
      - Miscellaneous Austrian cities, 1898, 1925-1926, undated (Box 54, Folder 611)
    - Brazil, 1956-1958, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 612)
    - Canada
      - Toronto
        - Royal Opera House, 1881 (Box 54, Folder 613)
        - Miscellaneous Toronto theaters (G-T); unidentified, 1881-1882, undated (Box 54, Folder 614)
      - Miscellaneous Canadian cities (H-M); unidentified, 1880, 1891, undated (Box 54, Folder 615)
    - China, undated (Box 54, Folder 616)
    - Cuba, 1877, undated (Box 54, Folder 617)
    - Czechoslovakia
      - Prague, 1912, 1925 (Box 54, Folder 618)
    - Denmark
      - Copenhagen
        - Tivoli, 1892, 1899 (Box 54, Folder 619)
    - France
      - Paris
        - Théâtre de la Port-Saint-Martin, 1961-1966, undated (Box 54, Folder 620-621)
        - Théâtre Khédivial de 1'Opéra, 1910, undated (Box 54, Folder 622)
        - Miscellaneous Paris theaters (A-G1), 1892-1899, 1921, 1958, undated (Box 55, Folder 623)
        - Miscellaneous Paris theaters (Gr-O), 1931, 1964-1966, undated (Box 55, Folder 624)
        - Miscellaneous Paris theaters (T), 1907-1908, 1911, 1921 (Box 55, Folder 625)
        - Unidentified Paris, 1921, 1959-1960, undated (Box 55, Folder 626)
      - Miscellaneous French cities (O); unidentified, 1931, undated (Box 55, Folder 627)
    - Germany
      - Bad Kissengen, 1907 (Box 55, Folder 628)
      - Berlin, 1891-1903, 1912, undated (Box 55, Folder 629)
      - Dresden, 1884-1908 (Box 55, Folder 630)
      - Munich, 1907, 1912, 1928-1930 (Box 55, Folder 631)
      - Miscellaneous German cities (B- S); unidentified, 1896, 1903-1907 (Box 55, Folder 632)
    - Greece, 1882 (Box 56, Folder 633)
    - Hungary, 1885, 1925, undated (Box 56, Folder 634)
    - India
      - Calcutta, 1874 (Box 56, Folder 635)
      - Isle of Man, 1863 (Box 56, Folder 636)
    - Italy
      - Rome, 1894, 1925-1926 (Box 56, Folder 637)
      - Verona, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 638)
      - Miscellaneous Italian cities (F-N), 1894, undated (Box 56, Folder 639)
    - Mexico
      - Mexico City, 1935, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 640-644)
      - Unidentified Mexico, 1911-1912 (Box 57, Folder 645)
    - Netherlands, 1911-1912 (Box 57, Folder 646)
    - New Zealand
      - Dunedin, 1901 (Box 57, Folder 647)
    - Sweden
      - Stockholm, 1930 (Box 57, Folder 648)
    - Switzerland, 1896, 1908, undated (Box 57, Folder 649)
    - Turkey
      - Constantinople
        - Opéra Comique (appearances by Comédie Française de Paris), 1895 (Box 57, Folder 650)
  - Subseries D:, 1861-1989; Series I; 192 linear feet (461 boxes) Largest dimension: 12"
    The material within this subseries is arranged chronologically by year; within each year material is arranged alphabetically by city (Material is not categorized by country; within any one year, for example, Boston would follow Berlin); within each city material is alphabetically arranged by title of production. Programs for soloist performances are filed under the name of the soloist rather than under a production title. Variety and vaudeville performances are filed under those terms rather than under a production title. Amateur and summer stock company productions are filed either under the name of the company or under the production title.
    Undated material, and dated material with an unidentified production location, follows the main run of material. Undated material is arranged by title of production after country, state, and city. Dated material with an unidentified production location is arranged alphabetically by title of production.
    - 1861 Baltimore, MD - 1863 Saratoga, NY (Box 58)
    - 1864 Boston, MA - 1866 Boston, MA (Box 59)
    - 1866 Liverpool, England - 1867 Philadelphia, PA (Box 60)
    - 1868 Boston, MA - 1868 Philadelphia, PA (Box 61)
    - 1869 Berlin, Germany - 1870 Boston, MA (F) (Box 62)
    - 1870 Boston, MA (G) - 1871 London, England (M) (Box 63)
    - 1871 London, England (P) - 1872 New York, NY (J) (Box 64)
    - 1872 New York, NY (L) - 1873 New York, NY (S) (Box 65)
    - 1873 New York, NY (T) - 1875 London, England (H) (Box 66)
    - 1875 London, England (J) - 1876 Bristol, England (Box 67)
    - 1876 Chicago, IL - 1876 New York, NY (R) (Box 68)
    - 1876 New York, NY (S) - 1877 New Haven, CT (H) (Box 69)
    - 1877 New Haven, CT (P) - 1878 London, England (H) (Box 70)
    - 1878 London, England (L) - 1879 Boston, MA (F) (Box 71)
    - 1879 Boston, MA (H) - 1879 New York, NY (H) (Box 72)
    - 1879 New York, NY (I) - 1880 Liverpool, England (Box 73)
    - 1880 London, England - 1880 New York, NY (H) (Box 74)
    - 1880 New York, NY (L) - 1881 New Britain, CT (Box 75)
    - 1881 New Haven, CT - 1881 New York, NY (L) (Box 76)
    - 1881 New York, NY (M) - 1882 London, England (M) (Box 77)
    - 1882 London, England (O) - 1882 New York, NY (H) (Box 78)
    - 1882 New York, NY (I) - 1883 Kansas City, MO (Box 79)
    - 1883 London, England - 1883 New Haven, CT (Box 80)
    - 1883 New York, NY - 1883 Washington, D.C. (Bu) (Box 81)
    - 1883 Washington, D.C. (C) - 1884 Montreal, Canada (Box 82)
    - 1884 New Bedford, MA - 1884 New Haven, CT (U) (Box 83)
    - 1884 New Haven, CT (V) - 1884 Washington, D.C. (C1) (Box 84)
    - 1884 Washington, D.C. (Co) - 1885 Nantucket Island, MA (Box 85)
    - 1885 New Haven, CT (A-P) (Box 86)
    - 1885 New Haven, CT (R) - 1885 New York, NY (P) (Box 87)
    - 1885 New York, NY (R) - 1886 Boston, MA (H) (Box 88)
    - 1886 Boston, MA (J) - 1886 New Haven, CT (S) (Box 89)
    - 1886 New Haven, CT (T) - 1886 New York, NY (S) (Box 90)
    - 1886 New York, NY (T) - 1887 Minneapolis, MN (Box 91)
    - 1887 New Bedford, MA - 1887 New York, NY (M) (Box 92)
    - 1887 New York, NY (N) - 1888 London, England (C) (Box 93)
    - 1888 London, England (D) - 1888 New York, NY (A) (Box 94)
    - 1888 New York, NY (B-V) (Box 95)
    - 1888 New York, NY (W) - 1889 Minneapolis, MN (Box 96)
    - 1889 New Haven, CT - 1889 New York, NY (K) (Box 97)
    - 1889 New York, NY (L) - 1890 Boston, MA (Q) (Box 98)
    - 1890 Boston, MA (S) - 1890 New York, NY (A) (Box 99)
    - 1890 New York, NY (B-W) (Box 100)
    - 1890 Philadelphia, PA - 1891 London, England (B) (Box 101)
    - 1891 London, England (C) - 1891 New York, NY (C) (Box 102)
    - 1891 New York, NY (D-V) (Box 103)
    - 1891 New York, NY (W) - 1892 Boston, MA (S) (Box 104)
    - 1892 Boston, MA (T) - 1892 New Haven, CT (G) (Box 105)
    - 1892 New Haven, CT (J) - 1892 New York, NY (R) (Box 106)
    - 1892 New York, NY (S) - 1893 Boston, MA (M) (Box 107)
    - 1892 Boston, MA (O) - 1893 London, England (Box 108)
    - 1893 Louisville, KY - 1893 New York, NY (L) (Box 109)
    - 1893 New York, NY (M) - 1894 Boston, MA (G) (Box 110)
    - 1894 Boston, MA (H) - 1894 London, England (F) (Box 111)
    - 1894 London, England (G) - 1894 New York, NY (B) (Box 112)
    - 1894 New York, NY (C-W) (Box 113)
    - 1894 Paris, France - 1895 Boston, MA (R) (Box 114)
    - 1895 Boston, MA (S) - 1895 New Haven, CT (F) (Box 115)
    - 1895 New Haven, CT (H) - 1895 New York, NY (J) (Box 116)
    - 1895 New York, NY (K) - 1896 Boston, MA (C) (Box 117)
    - 1896 Boston, MA (D) - 1896 London, England (M) (Box 118)
    - 1896 London, England (P) - 1896 New York, NY (B) (Box 119)
    - 1896 New York, NY (C) - 1896 Philadelphia, PA (M) (Box 120)
    - 1896 Philadelphia, PA (N) - 1897 London, England (K) (Box 121)
    - 1897 London, England (L) - 1897 New York, NY (B) (Box 122)
    - 1897 New York, NY (C-Ve) (Box 123)
    - 1897 New York, NY (W) - 1898 Galveston, TX (Box 124)
    - 1898 Hartford, CT - 1898 New Haven, CT (B) (Box 125)
    - 1898 New Haven, CT (C) - 1898 New York, NY (H) (Box 126)
    - 1898 New York, NY (I) - 1898 Winthrop, MA (Box 127)
    - 1899 Baltimore, MD - 1899 Liverpool, England (Box 128)
    - 1899 London, England - 1899 New Haven, CT (K) (Box 129)
    - 1899 New Haven, CT (L) - 1899 New York, NY (K) (Box 130)
    - 1899 New York, NY (L-V) (Box 131)
    - 1899 New York, NY (W) - 1900 Boston, MA (O) (Box 132)
    - 1900 Boston, MA (P) - 1900 London, England (M) (Box 133)
    - 1900 London, England (N) - 1900 New Haven, CT (Q) (Box 134)
    - 1900 New Haven, CT - 1900 New York, NY (Mr) (Box 135)
    - 1900 New York, NY (My) - 1900 Portland, OR (L) (Box 136)
    - 1900 Portland, OR (M) - 1901 Boston, MA (Box 137)
    - 1901 Buffalo, NY - 1901 London, England (S) (Box 138)
    - 1901 London, England (T) - 1901 New Haven, CT (S) (Box 139)
    - 1901 New Haven, CT (T) - 1901 New York, NY (P) (Box 140)
    - 1901 New York, NY (Q) - 1902 Baltimore, MD (Box 141)
    - 1902 Berlin, Germany - 1902 Boston, MA (Box 142)
    - 1902 Bryn Mawr, PA - 1902 London, England (E) (Box 143)
    - 1902 London, England (F) - 1902 Naples, Italy (Box 144)
    - 1902 New Haven, CT (Box 145)
    - 1902 New York, NY (A-O) (Box 146)
    - 1902 New York, NY (P) - 1903 Boston, MA (E) (Box 147)
    - 1903 Boston, MA (G) - 1903 Leatherhead, England (Box 148)
    - 1903 London, England - 1903 Lynn, MA (Box 149)
    - 1903 New Britain, CT - 1903 New York, NY (B) (Box 150)
    - 1903 New York, NY (C) - 1903 New York, NY (P) (Box 151)
    - 1903 New York, NY (R) - 1904 Boston, MA (B) (Box 152)
    - 1904 Boston, MA (C) - 1904 London, England (B) (Box 153)
    - 1904 London, England (C) - 1904 London, England (Va) (Box 154)
    - 1904 London, England (Ve) - 1904 New York, NY (H) (Box 155)
    - 1904 New York, NY (I) - 1904 New York, NY (Y) (Box 156)
    - 1904 Nottingham, England - 1905 Boston, MA (M) (Box 157)
    - 1905 Boston, MA (R) - 1905 London, England (J) (Box 158)
    - 1905 London, England (K) - 1905 New Haven, CT (S) (Box 159)
    - 1905 New Haven, CT (W) - 1905 New York, NY (M) (Box 160)
    - 1905 New York, NY (N) - 1905 Paris, France (Box 161)
    - 1905 Philadelphia, PA - 1906 Boston, MA (H) (Box 162)
    - 1906 Boston, MA (J) - 1906 London, England (A) (Box 163)
    - 1906 London, England (B-Va) (Box 164)
    - 1906 London, England (Ve) - 1906 New York, NY (E) (Box 165)
    - 1906 New York, NY (F-Ri) (Box 166)
    - 1906 New York, NY (Ro) - 1906 Springfield, MA (U) (Box 167)
    - 1906 Springfield, MA (V) - 1907 Boston, MA (K) (Box 168)
    - 1907 Boston, MA (L) - 1907 Chicago, IL (Box 169)
    - 1907 Cleveland, OH - 1907 New Haven, CT (T) (Box 170)
    - 1907 New Haven, CT (V) - 1907 New York, NY (La) (Box 171)
    - 1907 New York, NY (Li-R) (Box 172)
    - 1907 New York, NY (S) - 1907 Springfield, MA (H) (Box 173)
    - 1907 Springfield, MA (I) - 1908 Boston, MA (J) (Box 174)
    - 1908 Boston, MA (L) - 1908 Hartford, CT (Box 175)
    - 1908 Kansas City, MO - 1908 New Haven, CT (G) (Box 176)
    - 1908 New Haven, CT (H) - 1908 New York, NY (H) (Box 177)
    - 1908 New York, NY (I-T) (Box 178)
    - 1908 New York, NY (V) - 1908 Worchester, MA (Box 179)
    - 1909 Boston, MA (A-S) (Box 180)
    - 1909 Boston, MA (T) - 1909 New Haven, CT (C) (Box 181)
    - 1909 New Haven, CT (C) - 1909 New York, NY (C) (Box 182)
    - 1909 New York, NY (D-N) (Box 183)
    - 1909 New York, NY (0) - 1909 Paris, France (L) (Box 184)
    - 1909 Paris, France (M) - 1910 Boston, MA (B) (Box 185)
    - 1910 Boston, MA (C-Se) (Box 186)
    - 1910 Boston, MA (Sh) - 1910 Munich, Germany (Box 187)
    - 1910 New Haven, CT - 1910 New York, NY (Ci) (Box 188)
    - 1910 New York, NY (Co-Po) (Box 189)
    - 1910 New York, NY (Pr) - 1910 Paris, France (M) (Box 190)
    - 1910 Paris, France (R) - 1911 Boston, MA (F) (Box 191)
    - 1911 Boston, MA (G) - 1911 Cambridge, MA (Box 192)
    - 1911 Chicago, IL - 1911 Madison, WI (Box 193)
    - 1911 Munich, Germany - 1911 New York, NY (A) (Box 194)
    - 1911 New York, NY (B-M) (Box 195)
    - 1911 New York, NY (N) - 1911 Saint Louis, MO (Box 196)
    - 1911 Salem, MA - 1912 Boston, MA (F) (Box 197)
    - 1912 Boston, MA (G) - 1912 Dublin, Ireland (Box 198)
    - 1912 Hartford, CT - 1912 New Haven, CT (L) (Box 199)
    - 1912 New Haven, CT (M) - 1912 New York, NY (G) (Box 200)
    - 1912 New York, NY (H-S1) (Box 201)
    - 1912 New York, NY (Sn) - 1912 Springfield, MA (Box 202)
    - 1912 Syracuse, NY - 1913 Boston, MA (B) (Box 203)
    - 1913 Boston, MA (C) - 1913 Larchmont, NY (Box 204)
    - 1913 Lakeville, CT - 1913 London, England (V) (Box 205)
    - 1913 London, England (W) - 1913 New York, NY (A) (Box 206)
    - 1913 New York, NY (B-S) (Box 207)
    - 1913 New York, NY (T) - 1913 Syracuse, NY (O) (Box 208)
    - 1913 Syracuse, NY (P) - 1914 Boston, MA (N) (Box 209)
    - 1914 Boston, MA (P) - 1914 Hartford, CT (S) (Box 210)
    - 1914 Hartford, CT (T) - 1914 Milwaukee, WI (Box 211)
    - 1914 New Haven, CT (A-W) (Box 212)
    - 1914 New London, CT - 1914 New York, NY (L) (Box 213)
    - 1914 New York, NY (M-S) (Box 214)
    - 1914 New York, NY (T) - 1914 Paris, France (Box 215)
    - 1914 Philadelphia, PA - 1915 Boston, MA (E) (Box 216)
    - 1915 Boston, MA (G-Y) (Box 217)
    - 1915 Bridgeport, CT - 1915 London, England (M) (Box 218)
    - 1915 London, England (S) - 1915 New Haven, CT (M) (Box 219)
    - 1915 New Haven, CT (O) - 1915 New York, NY (C1) (Box 220)
    - 1915 New York, NY (Co-M) (Box 221)
    - 1915 New York, NY (N-V) (Box 222)
    - 1915 New York, NY (W) - 1916 Boston, MA (O) (Box 223)
    - 1916 Boston, MA (P) - 1916 London, England (Box 224)
    - 1916 Newark, NJ - 1916 New Haven, CT (S) (Box 225)
    - 1916 New Haven, CT (T) - 1916 New York, NY (G) (Box 226)
    - 1916 New York, NY (H-Ro) (Box 227)
    - 1916 New York, NY (Ru) - 1917 Boston, MA (C) (Box 228)
    - 1917 Boston, MA (D) - 1917 Grand Forks, ND (Box 229)
    - 1917 Hanover, NH - 1917 New Haven, CT (E) (Box 230)
    - 1917 New Haven, CT (F) - 1917 New York, NY (C) (Box 231)
    - 1917 New York, NY (D-N) (Box 232)
    - 1917 New York, NY (O) - 1917 Yonkers, NY (Box 233)
    - 1918 Boston, MA (B) - 1918 Hartford, CT (N) (Box 234)
    - 1918 Hartford, CT (O) - 1918 New Haven, CT (N) (Box 235)
    - 1918 New Haven, CT (O) - 1918 New York, NY (G) (Box 236)
    - 1918 New York, NY (H-S) (Box 237)
    - 1918 New York, NY (T) - 1919 Boston, MA (R) (Box 238)
    - 1919 Boston, MA (S) - 1919 New Haven, CT (C) (Box 239)
    - 1919 New Haven, CT (D-W) (Box 240)
    - 1919 New York, NY (A-M) (Box 241)
    - 1919 New York, NY (N) - 1919 Tours, France (Box 242)
    - 1919 Washington, D.C. - 1920 London, England (O) (Box 243)
    - 1920 London, England (P) - 1920 New Haven, CT (Box 244)
    - 1920 New York, NY (A-L) (Box 245)
    - 1920 New York, NY (M) - 1920 Philadelphia, PA (Box 246)
    - 1920 Springfield, MA - 1921 Detroit, MI (Box 247)
    - 1921 Grand Rapids, MI-1921 Montreal, Canada (Box 248)
    - 1921 New Haven, CT - 1921 New York, NY (E) (Box 249)
    - 1921 New York, NY (F - Th) (Box 250)
    - 1921 New York, NY (Ti)-1922 Boston, MA (F) (Box 251)
    - 1922 Boston, MA (G) - 1922 London, England (C) (Box 252)
    - 1922 London, England (D) - 1922 New Haven, CT (R) (Box 253)
    - 1922 New Haven, CT (S) - 1922 New York, NY (G) (Box 254)
    - 1922 New York, NY (H-Se) (Box 255)
    - 1922 New York, NY (Sh) - 1923 Boston, MA (C) (Box 256)
    - 1923 Boston, MA (D) - 1923 London, England(L) (Box 257)
    - 1923 London, England (M) - 1923 New Haven, CT (M) (Box 258)
    - 1923 New Haven, CT (N) - 1923 New York, NY (F) (Box 259)
    - 1923 New York, NY (G-P) (Box 260)
    - 1923 New York, NY (Q-Z) (Box 261)
    - 1923 Norfolk, VA - 1924 Boston, MA (Box 262)
    - 1924 Brussels, Belgium - 1924 London, England (T) (Box 263)
    - 1924 London, England (V) - 1924 New Haven, CT (R) (Box 264)
    - 1924 New Haven, CT (S) - 1924 New York, NY (Gr) (Box 265)
    - 1924 New York, NY (Gu-R) (Box 266)
    - 1924 New York, NY (S) - 1924 Peterborough, NH (Box 267)
    - 1924 Philadelphia, PA - 1925 London, England (D) (Box 268)
    - 1925 London, England (F) - 1925 Minneapolis, MN (Box 269)
    - 1925 New Haven, CT (A-P) (Box 270)
    - 1925 New Haven, CT (R) - 1925 New York, NY (C) (Box 271)
    - 1925 New York, NY (D-M) (Box 272)
    - 1925 New York, NY (N-Z) (Box 273)
    - 1925 Norfolk, VA - 1926 Boston, MA (S) (Box 274)
    - 1926 Boston, MA (T) - 1926 London, England (T) (Box 275)
    - 1926 London, England (V) - 1926 New Haven, CT (M) (Box 276)
    - 1926 New Haven, CT (N) - 1926 New York, NY (C) (Box 277)
    - 1926 New York, NY (D-K) (Box 278)
    - 1926 New York, NY (L-S) (Box 279)
    - 1926 New York, NY (T) - 1926 Washington, DC (Box 280)
    - 1927 Aix-les-Bains, France - 1927 Frankfurt, Germany (Box 281)
    - 1927 Hamburg, Germany - 1927 London, England (M) (Box 282)
    - 1927 London, England (0) - 1927 New Haven, CT (H) (Box 283)
    - 1927 New Haven, CT (I) - 1927 New York, NY (B) (Box 284)
    - 1927 New York, NY (C-K) (Box 285)
    - 1927 New York, NY (L-P) (Box 286)
    - 1927 New York, NY (Q) - 1927 Northampton, MA (Box 287)
    - 1927 Paris, France - 1928 Boston, MA (M) (Box 288)
    - 1928 Boston, MA (P) - 1928 London, England (T) (Box 289)
    - 1928 London, England (V) - 1928 New Haven, CT (L) (Box 290)
    - 1928 New Haven, CT (M) - 1928 New York, NY (A) (Box 291)
    - 1928 New York, NY (B-G) (Box 292)
    - 1928 New York, NY (H-Pe) (Box 293)
    - 1928 New York, NY (Pl-V) (Box 294)
    - 1928 New York, NY (W) - 1929 Berlin, Germany (Box 295)
    - 1929 Boston, MA - 1929 Jersey City, NJ (Box 296)
    - 1929 London, England - 1929 New Haven, CT (G) (Box 297)
    - 1929 New Haven, CT (H-Y) (Box 298)
    - 1929 New York, NY (A-F) (Box 299)
    - 1929 New York, NY (G-Mu) (Box 300)
    - 1929 New York, NY (My-S) (Box 301)
    - 1929 New York, NY (T) - 1929 Waterbury, CT (Box 302)
    - 1930 Aix-les-Bains, France - 1930 Holyoke, MA (Box 303)
    - 1930 Indianapolis, IN - 1930 London, England (R) (Box 304)
    - 1930 London, England (S) - 1930 New Haven, CT (N) (Box 305)
    - 1930 New Haven, CT (0) - 1930 New York, NY (D) (Box 306)
    - 1930 New York, NY (E-L) (Box 307)
    - 1930 New York, NY (M-Sm) (Box 308)
    - 1930 New York, NY (So) - 1930 Paris, France (Box 309)
    - 1930 Pasadena, CA - 1931 Indianapolis, IN (M) (Box 310)
    - 1931 Indianapolis, IN (N) - 1931 Madison, CT (Box 311)
    - 1931 New Haven, CT (A-S) (Box 312)
    - 1931 New Haven, CT (T) - 1931 New York, NY (C) (Box 313)
    - 1931 New York, NY (D-M) (Box 314)
    - 1931 New York, NY (N-T) (Box 315)
    - 1931 New York, NY (V) - 1931 York, England (Box 316)
    - 1932 Athens, Greece - 1932 London, England (G) (Box 317)
    - 1932 London, England (H) - 1932 New Haven, CT (E) (Box 318)
    - 1932 New Haven, CT (F) - 1932 New York, NY (A) (Box 319)
    - 1932 New York, NY (B-F) (Box 320)
    - 1932 New York, NY (G-S) (Box 321)
    - 1932 New York, NY (T) - 1933 Boston, MA (Box 322)
    - 1933 Chapel Hill, NC - 1933 New Haven, CT (B) (Box 323)
    - 1933 New Haven, CT (C) - 1933 New York, NY (C) (Box 324)
    - 1933 New York, NY (D-M) (Box 325)
    - 1933 New York, NY (N) - 1933 Saint Louis, MO (Box 326)
    - 1933 San Francisco, CA - 1934 London, England (N) (Box 327)
    - 1934 London, England (Q) - 1934 New Haven, CT (L) (Box 328)
    - 1934 New Haven, CT (M) - 1934 New York, NY (Di) (Box 329)
    - 1934 New York, NY (Do-M) (Box 330)
    - 1934 New York, NY (N-Z) (Box 331)
    - 1934 Ogunquit, ME - 1935 Detroit, MI (Box 332)
    - 1935 Great Malvern, England - 1935 New Haven, CT (J) (Box 333)
    - 1935 New Haven, CT (L) - 1935 New York, NY (C) (Box 334)
    - 1935 New York, NY (D-M) (Box 335)
    - 1935 New York, NY (N-T) (Box 336)
    - 1935 New York, NY (V) - 1936 Chapel Hill, NC (Box 337)
    - 1936 Chicago, IL - 1936 London, England (K) (Box 338)
    - 1936 London, England (L) - 1936 New Haven, CT (Box 339)
    - 1936 New York, NY (A-H) (Box 340)
    - 1936 New York, NY (I-S) (Box 341)
    - 1936 New York, NY (T) - 1937 Boston, MA (M) (Box 342)
    - 1937 Boston, MA (P) - 1937 New Haven, CT (G) (Box 343)
    - 1937 New Haven, CT (H) - 1937 New York, NY (G) (Box 344)
    - 1937 New York, NY (H-S) (Box 345)
    - 1937 New York, NY (T) - 1937 Westport, CT (Box 346)
    - 1938 Boston, MA - 1938 Madison, CT (Box 347)
    - 1938 Matunuck, RI - 1938 New York, NY (F) (Box 348)
    - 1938 New York, NY (G-R) (Box 349)
    - 1938 New York, NY (S) - 1938 Westport, CT (Box 350)
    - 1939 Boston, MA - 1939 Lakewood, ME (Box 351)
    - 1939 London, England - 1939 New York, NY (A) (Box 352)
    - 1939 New York, NY (B-R) (Box 353)
    - 1939 New York, NY (S) - 1939 Woodstock, NY (Box 354)
    - 1940 Banff, Canada - 1940 New Haven, CT (J) (Box 355)
    - 1940 New Haven, CT (K) - 1940 New York, NY (F) (Box 356)
    - 1940 New York, NY (G-M) (Box 357)
    - 1940 New York, NY (N) - 1940 Westport, CT (Box 358)